http://www.advanceddisposal.com/privacy-policy.aspx

Attention Customers: We're excited to announce that Waste Management, North America's leading environmental solutions provider, has acquired Advanced Disposal. Learn what this means for you here.
Find a Facility
For Business
Collection Services
Garbage
Recycling
Special Waste
Construction & Demolition
Disposal & Recycling Services
2020
Waste Management and Advanced Disposal Announce Revised Terms of Acquisition and Agreement to Sell Substantially All Anticipated Regulatory Divestitures to GFL Environmental
Advanced Disposal Announces First Quarter Results
Advanced Disposal Announces Fourth Quarter Results
Advanced Disposal Announces Second Quarter Results
ADVANCED DISPOSAL SERVICES, INC. STOCKHOLDERS APPROVE REVISED TERMS OF ACQUISITION BY WASTE MANAGEMENT, INC.
Waste Management Completes $4.6 Billion Acquisition of Advanced Disposal
2019
Advanced Disposal Announces Fourth Quarter Results (1)
News Release - Waste Management to Acquire Advanced Disposal for $4.9 Billion
Advanced Disposal Sets Date for Second Quarter 2019 Earnings Release
Advanced Disposal Services, Inc. Stockholders Approve Acquisition by Waste Management, Inc.
Advanced Disposal Announces First Quarter Results
Advanced Disposal Announces Second Quarter Results
Advanced Disposal Announces Third Quarter Results
2018
Advanced Disposal To Attend Gabelli & Company's Waste & Environmental Services Symposium
Advanced Disposal Completes Secondary Offering Of Common Stock
Advanced Disposal Announces Secondary Offering of Common Stock
Advanced Disposal Announces Fourth Quarter Results
Advanced Disposal Appoints Ernest J. Mrozek To Its Board Of Directors
Advanced Disposal Sets Date for Fourth Quarter 2017 Earnings Call
2017
Advanced Disposal Announces A Change To Its Board Of Directors As It Continues To Enhance Board Independence
Advanced Disposal To Attend Credit Suisse Industrials Conference
Advanced Disposal Completes Secondary Offering of Common Stock and Closes Debt Refinancing
Advanced Disposal Announces Secondary Offering of Common Stock
Advanced Disposal Announces Entry Into New Indiana Market Through Acquisition of CGS Services
Advanced Disposal Announces First Quarter Results
Advanced Disposal Announces Fourth Quarter Results
Advanced Disposal Announces That Michael J. Hoffman Has Been Elected to Its Board
Advanced Disposal Announces Upsize and Pricing of Secondary Public Offering of Common Stock
Advanced Disposal Finalizes Amendment to Senior Secured Credit Facility Resulting in 0.5% Reduction in Term Loan Debt
Advanced Disposal Sets Date for First Quarter 2017 Earnings Call
Advanced Disposal Sets Date for Fourth Quarter 2016 Earnings Call
News Release - Advanced Disposal Opens New Operations Facility in Orlando, Fla.
2016
Advanced Disposal's Flag Retirement Program Collects Over 4,500 Flags in Second Year
Advanced Disposal Acquires West Mobile Sanitation
Advanced Disposal Hires Wesley A. Salmons as New Director of Corporate Safety and Compliance
Advanced Disposal Announces Second Quarter Results
Advanced Disposal Announces Investment by Canada Pension Plan Investment Board and Michael Koen Joining the Board of Directors
Advanced Disposal Sets Date for Second Quarter 2016 Earnings Call
Advanced Disposal Announces 2016 Ponte Vedra High School SALC Scholarship Winners
Advanced Disposal Promotes Jay Warzinski to Vice President of Landfill Operations
Advanced DIsposal Launches Second Annual American Flag Retirement Program
Advanced Disposal to Attend Waste Expo Investor Summit and Stifel Industrials Conference
Advanced Disposal Announces Changes to Board of Directors
Advanced Disposal Begins Trash and Recycling Collection in the City of Howell on Feb. 1, 2016
Advanced Disposal Proudly Supports Industry Safety by Participating in National Safety Stand-Down
Advanced Disposal Honors Top Employees at Annual Employee of the Year Celebration
Advanced Disposal Drivers Save Pickney Home From Burning
Advanced Disposal Begins Macon, Ga. Residential Waste Management Services on Jan. 4, 2016
Advanced Disposal Begins Trash Collection in Fayette City, Pa. on January 4, 2016
Advanced Disposal Announces Third Quarter Results
Advanced Disposal Begins Trash Collection in West Easton, Pa. on January 7, 2016
Advanced Disposal Begins Trash, Yard Waste and Single-Stream Recycling Collection in Prestbury, Ill. on January 6, 2016
Advanced Disposal Begins Trash, Single-Stream Recycling and Yard Waste Collection in Roscoe, Ill. on January 5, 2016
Advanced Disposal Begins Trash Collection in Sherwood, Wis. on January 14, 2016
Advanced Disposal Acquires FDS Disposal, LLC
Advanced Disposal Commences Initial Public Offering of Common Stock (1)
Advanced Disposal Prices Initial Public Offering of Common Stock
Advanced Disposal Sets Date for Third Quarter 2016 Earnings Call
Advanced Disposal Completes Initial Public Offering of Common Stock
Advanced Disposal Announces Changes to Board of Directors (1)
Advanced Disposal Considers Potential Debt Refinancing
Advanced Disposal Services, Inc. Announces Proposed Senior Notes Offering
Advanced Disposal Commences Cash Tender Offer For Any and All of its Outstanding 8 1/4% Senior Notes Due 2020
Advanced Disposal Services, Inc. Prices Offering of $425 Million of 5 5/8% Senior Notes Due 2024
Advanced Disposal Announces Underwriters' Exercise of Option to Purchase Additional Shares in Connection with Initial Public Offering
Advanced Disposal Announces Third Quarter Results (1)
2015
Advanced Disposal Begins Macon, Ga. Residential Waste Management Services on Jan. 4, 2016
Advanced Disposal Begins Trash Collection in Grove Hill, Ala. on January 2, 2016
Advanced Disposal Presented a Donation to K9s for Warriors This Morning for $12,500
Advanced Disposal Welcomes Zachary Salata as Vice President of Financial Reporting
Advanced Disposal Acquires Earth First, LLC and Enters Fort Wayne, Indiana Market
ADVANCED DISPOSAL ACQUIRES WEBB WASTE, INC.
Advanced Disposal Acquires AC Sanitation, Inc.
Advanced Disposal Opens Ninth Compressed Natural Gas Station in Batavia
Advanced Disposal Hosts Flag Retirement Ceremony in Honor of Veterans Day
Advanced Disposal's Stone's Throw Landfill Named Landfill of the Year
Advanced Disposal Acquires Williams Sanitation Services
Advanced Disposal Announces Third Quarter Results
Advanced Disposal Welcomes Jerry Kreuzman as General Manager to Melrose Park Facility
Advanced Disposal Opens Eighth Compressed Natural Gas Station in Hartland
Advanced Disposal Sets Date for Third Quarter 2015 Earnings Call
Advanced Disposal Welcomes Rakesh Gupta as Vice President of Information Technology
Advanced Disposal Welcomes Brian Chesson as General Manager to Atlanta North Facility
Advanced Disposal Opens Compressed Natural Gas Station in Macon
Advanced Disposal Hosts Stakeholder Rally at Glacier Ridge Landfill
Advanced Disposal Presented with Job Creator Award by Governor Rick Scott
Advanced Disposal Announces the Filing of a Registration Statement for a Proposed Offering of Common Stock
Advanced Disposal Announces Second Quarter Results
Advanced Disposal CMO Mary O’Brien Announced as 2015 Woman of Influence
Advanced Disposal Driver Tony Barcellona Retires After 50 Years En Route
Advanced Disposal Welcomes Jeffrey Everett as Vice President and Assistant General Counsel
Advanced Disposal's Eco Man Makes Appearance at Campbellsport Library
Advanced Disposal Helps World Changers by Donating 17 Dumpsters for Home Renovations
Advanced Disposal Gives Back To St. Johns County By Providing Affordable Housing In Partnership With Habitat For Humanity
Advanced Disposal Celebrates Independence Day with Flag Retirement Program
Advanced Disposal Sets Date for Second Quarter 2015 Earnings Call
Advanced Disposal Acquires Ross Disposal Services
Advanced Disposal Announces Greg Huntington as Municipal Marketing and Government Affairs Manager
Keep the Stars & Stripes Bright This Flag Day
Advanced Disposal Salutes Employee's Daughter for Being Selected for $5,000 Scholarship
Advanced Disposal's Scott Gordon Recognized as Driver of the Year by National Waste & Recycling Association
Advanced Disposal Acquires Disposal Management Systems, Inc.
Advanced Disposal to Present at WasteExpo Investor Summit
Advanced Disposal's Kirstyn Shepler Earns Certified Risk Management Certification
Advanced Disposal Upgrades St. Johns County Residents' Curbside Recycling Program with Carts
Advanced Disposal Promotes Mike Stoeckigt as District Manager in North Wisconsin and Missouri
Advanced Disposal Invites Citizens and Businesses to Properly Retire Their American Flags With Honor
Advanced Disposal Announces PVHS SALC Scholarship Award Winners
Advanced Disposal Welcomes Jody Jackson as General Manager
Advanced Disposal Announces Jim Alderman as General Manager
Advanced Disposal Partners with Sarasota County for Landfill Open House and Ribbon Cutting Event
Advanced Disposal Announces First Quarter Results
Advanced Disposal Welcomes Alan Lovett as Chief Audit Executive/Vice President - Internal Audit
Advanced Disposal Acquires Little Hoppers
Advanced Disposal Asks "Are You Recycling Right?"
Advanced Disposal Landfill Operator Wins First Place in SWANA Road-E-O Competition
Advanced Disposal Welcomes Gary Parker As East Region Sales Manager
Advanced Disposal Sets Date for First Quarter 2015 Earnings Call
Advanced Disposal Acquires Rock Disposal, Inc.
Advanced Disposal Honors Excellence by Sponsoring Scholarships to Ponte Vedra High School Student Athletes
Advanced Disposal's Barbara Martin Earns Substance Abuse Program Administrator Certification
Advanced Disposal Announces Fourth Quarter and Full Year 2014 Year End Results
Advanced Disposal Welcomes William Soffera As
Senior Vice President – Special Projects
Advanced Disposal Honors Top Employees at Annual Employee of the Year Celebration
Advanced Disposal Appoints Finance Team
Advanced Disposal Promotes Matthew Parker to General Manager of Western Pennsylvania Facilities
Advanced Disposal Welcomes John Cunningham As General Manager
Advanced Disposal Sets Date for Annual 2014 Earnings Call
Advanced Disposal Acquires Pea Ridge Waste Management
Advanced Disposal Acquires Hornback Recycling & Disposal
2014
Advanced Disposal Staff Help Make Christmas Jolly for Children Through Local Charity
Advanced Disposal Welcomes Ray Kovas as Region Maintenance Manager
Advanced Disposal Welcomes Charlie Laws as General Manager
Advanced Disposal Recognizes and Thanks 22 Combat Warriors at Green Bay Packers NFL Game
Advanced Disposal Acquires Badger Disposal
Emerald Park Landfill Recertified as Wildlife Habitat Council Corporate Lands for Learning
Advanced Disposal Announces Highest Reported Quarterly Adjusted EBITDA Post Acquisition
Advanced Disposal Celebrates America Recycles Day with Document Shredding and Electronics Recycling Event for City of Detroit Residents
Advanced Disposal Acquires Weaver's Sanitation Services
Advanced Disposal Sets Date for Third Quarter 2014 Earnings Call
Advanced Disposal Makes Recycling Stylish as Presenting Sponsor for Love Your Mother Eco Fashion Show
Advanced Disposal Welcome Juan Romero as General Manager
Advanced Disposal Acquires Monroe's Rubbish Removal, Inc.
Advanced Disposal's Rolling Hills Landfill Annual Open House Draws Hundreds
Advanced Disposal Q2 2014 Earnings Release
Advanced Disposal Welcomes Susan Wilburn as South Region Sales Manager
Advanced Disposal Sets Date for Second Quarter 2014 Earnings Call
Advanced Disposal Appoints Senior Vice President, General Counsel
Advanced Disposal's Mauri Elledge Named ABC Marketing Professional of the Year
Advanced Disposal Promotes Jason Sturino
Advanced Disposal Welcomes Mike Galus
Advanced Disposal Welcomes Don Neukam as Vice President of Business Development and Strategic Planning
Advanced Disposal Promotes Mary Pat Stritof as Vice President of Information Technology
Advanced Disposal's Sam Safety Wants to Keep Kids Safe Around Garbage Trucks
Advanced Disposal Begins Servicing City of Detroit on Monday, June 2
Advanced Disposal Welcomes Dan Dewaard as Regional Manager
Advanced Disposal Promotes Randy Arnold to Senior Vice President - Operations and Landfills
Advanced Disposal Announces Eric VanHouten as General Manager of Detroit Facility
Advanced Disposal and Energy Systems Group Transform Georgia Waste into Fuel
Advanced Disposal Appoints CAO
Charlie Appleby Inducted into National Waste & Recycling Hall of Fame
Advanced Disposal Appoints COO
Earth Day is Every Day for Advanced Disposal's Environmental Heroes
Advanced Disposal Provides Scholarships to 12 High School Seniors, Encourages Furthering Education and Chasing Dreams
Advanced Disposal Partners with Keep Lee County Beautiful 25th Annual Great American Cleanup/Earth Day Trash Bash
Advanced Disposal's Wolf Creek Landfill Charters Cub Scout Pack 962
Advanced Disposal CEO Charlie Appleby Speaks to the Florida Leadership Academy at the University of Florida
Advanced Disposal Driver's Son Brings Home Gold and Inspires Others to Overcome Challenges
Advanced Disposal Honors Top Employees at Annual Employee of the Year Celebration
Advanced Disposal Purchases Assets From Roscoe Disposal, Further Expanding Illinois Footprint
Advanced Disposal Receives Two Grants from Pennsylvania to Convert Trucks to CNG
Advanced Disposal Welcomes Brian Beaudrie as Vice President of Maintenance
Advanced Disposal Welcomes Doug Coenen as Midwest Region Landfill Manager
Advanced Disposal Welcomes Mary Pat Stritof As Senior Director Of Information Technology Applications
Advanced Disposal Welcomes Doug Delp as District Sales & Municipal Marketing Manager
Advanced Disposal Acquires the Dumpster Company Assets, Further Expanding Greater Atlanta Footprint
Advanced Disposal Announces Erik Sankey as General Manager for Eastern Pennsylvania
Advanced Disposal Welcomes James Gebicki as Municipal Marketing and Government Affairs
Manager
Advanced Disposal Acquires Sherman Sanitation, Further Expanding Wisconsin Footprint
Advanced Disposal Acquires DC Disposal, Inc. Further Expanding Missouri Footprint
Advanced Disposal Promotes Michael Yelinek to Region Manager
2013
Advanced Disposal Welcomes Jeffrey Schneider as Director of Claims
Advanced Disposal's Marti Dickman named one of 2013's Women to Watch by Business Insurance
Advanced Disposal Promotes Brian Hahn to General Manager
Advanced Disposal Welcomes Josh Malek as Operations Manager
Advanced Disposal Welcomes Jeff Damon as Site Manager
Advanced Disposal Welcomes Bill Westrate as Vice President of Information Technology
Advanced Disposal National Accounts Welcomes Jim Bentley as General Manager
Advanced Disposal Acquires Cooper County Trash and MFG, LLC, Further Expanding Missouri Footprint
Advanced Disposal Promotes Michael Carlini to Sales Manager
Advanced Disposal Promotes Dominic Maruca to General Manager
Advanced Disposal Promotes Mark Van Weelden to General Manager
Advanced Disposal's Roscoe Transfer Station Now Open For Business
Advanced Disposal Welcomes Mark Fandel as Area Sales Manager
Advanced Disposal Welcomes John Somar as Financial Analyst
Advanced Disposal Welcomes Steven Bauer as Area Controller
Advanced Disposal Promotes Ed Yahner to East Region Marketing Manager
Advanced Disposal Welcomes Chad Basten as Sales Manager
Advanced Disposal Acquires Northern Waste, Inc., Further Expanding Wisconsin Footprint
Advanced Disposal Welcomes Scott Bradshaw as General Manager
Advanced Disposal Welcomes John O'Brien as Sales and Pricing Specialist
Advanced Disposal Promotes Dan Elplers to Area Sales Manager and Municipal Marketing Manager
Advanced Disposal Acquires Matchbox Disposal, Inc., Further Expanding Central Illinois Footprint
Advanced Disposal Welcomes Michael Kelly as Area Sales Manager
Advanced Disposal Welcomes Jodi Crom as Area Controller
Advanced Disposal Divests New York, New Jersey Assets to the Action Environmental Group
Advanced Disposal Promotes Jason Clemmons to Office Manager
Advanced Dispsoal Acquires AAA Sanitation, Inc., Further Expanding North Georgia Footprint
Advanced Disposal Acquires Assets of G & C Waste Services, Further Expanding Philadelphia Metro Footprint
Advanced Disposal Hires David Poleski as District Controller For Pennsylvania and Maryland
Advanced Disposal Welcomes Dustin Reynolds as General Manager in Madison
Advanced Disposal Promotes Christina Logan as Midwest Regional Safety Manager
Advanced Disposal Promotes Dave Rettell as East Region Landfill Manager
Governor Rick Scott Dedicates Advanced Disposal's Corporate Headquarters
Advanced Disposal Acquires Benson Disposal Fourth Midwest Region Acquisition in Less Than Two Weeks
Advanced Disposal Acquires Valdosta Waste, Expanding South Georgia Footprint
Advanced Disposal Expands in Pennsylvania Through Asset Purchase of Winsor Disposal
Advanced Disposal Closes Second Wisconsin Acquisition within the Week
Advanced Disposal Acquires Sheboygan Waste Materials, Expanding Eastern Wisconsin Footprint
Advanced Disposal Acquires Roscoe Transfer Station, Expanding Northern Illinois Footrpint
Advanced Disposal Welcomes Matt Neely as Midwest Region Landfill Manager
Advanced Disposal's Fresh Look for New Recycling Program
Advanced Disposal is Clean & Green Silver Level Sponsor of Blue Crab Festival
Advanced Disposal Acquires RW Edwards Solid Waste Division, Expanding Tennessee Footprint
Advanced Disposal Welcomes John Taddonio as Municipal Marketing & Government Affairs Manager
Chris Hagan Joins Advanced Disposal as Municipal and Government Affairs Manager
Advanced Disposal Extends Partnership With West Point
Advanced Disposal Midwest Run Out Hunger Kickoff
Advanced Disposal Presents Scholarships to 12 High School Seniors
Advanced Disposal Teams Up with the City of St. Augustine to Celebrate Earth Day
Advanced Disposal Welcomes Bill Wolfram as Regional Marketing and Government Affairs Manager
Advanced Disposal Promotes Mark Nighbor to Director of Marketing and Sales
Advanced Disposal Promotes Jeffrey Nie to Midwest Regional Sales Manager
Advanced Disposal Donates $40,000 in Office Furniture to Clay County Chamber of Commerce
Advanced Disposal Catches a Rising Star in Wesley Salmons
Advanced Disposal Welcomes John Spegal as Vice President Business Development
Advanced Disposal Welcomes Jennifer Klennert as Municipal & Government Affairs Manager
2012
Advanced Disposal Selects Northeast Florida as Company Headquarters
Advanced Disposal and Marengo High School "End Hunger in the End Zone"
Advanced Disposal's Emerald Park Landfill Receives Prestigious Corporate Lands for Learning Designation From Wildlife Habitat Council
Advanced Disposal Teams Up with Atlantic Beach to Celebrate America Recycles Day
Advanced Disposal Teams up with St. Johns County to Celebrate America Recycles Day at Second Annual Dounment Shredding Event
Advanced Disposal Expands to Tennessee with the Newly Acquired Eco-Safe Landfill
Advanced Disposal Celebrates 450th Commemoration with Expanded Recycling Program
Advanced Disposal to Collect Sold Waste Garbage Carts September 27, 28 & 29
Advanced Disposal Raises Awareness and Funds for Local Charities at First Annual Trash Day & Bash
Advanced Disposal and Interstate Waste Now Operating Under the Advanced Disposal Name
Advanced Disposal Suspends All Operations in Mobile and Biloxi Areas Due to Tropical Storm Isaac.
Advanced Disposal Announces Senior Leadership Team of Post Closing Consolidated Companies
A Cleaner, Greener Irmo with Advanced Disposal
Star Atlantic Waste Holdings Announces Agreement to Acquire Veolia ES Solid Waste
Advanced Disposal Brings Cleaner, Greener Waste Collection to Greater Atlanta
Advanced Disposal Grows Charlotte Footprint With Two Acquisitions
Advanced Disposal Acquires At Your Disposal, Inc. Further Expanding Company's North Georgia Operations
Advanced Disposal Begins Service to the Town of Orange Park on June 1
Advanced Disposal Unveils Landfill Gas-to-Energy Facility at Wolf Creek Landfill
Advanced Disposal Wants St. Augustine Beach Residents to Celebrate Earth Day by Recycling
Advanced Disposal's Sumrall Recycling Responds to Growing Popularity of Recycling with Efficiency
Advanced Disposal Presents Washington County with $750,000 Landfill Payment
Advanced Disposal Adds Five Drivers and One Mechanic to Alabama Operations
Advanced Disposal Opens $5 Million Recycling Facility Bringing 44 Jobs to Forsyth County
Advanced Disposal Bag Ladies Recycle 4,120 Pounds at 26.2 with Donna Marathon
Advanced Disposal Brings Recycling to Laurel, Mississippi
Free Recycling Now Available to ALL Advanced Disposal Customers in Nassau County
Advanced Disposal Now Collects 25 Recyclable Items from St. Augustine Beach Residents
2011
Advanced Disposal's Mobile Transfer Station Now Open for Business
22,000 Pounds of Paper Shredded and Recycled at Free Shredder Day
Advanced Disposal Grows Alabama Residential Customer Base with Lowndes Garbage Acquisition
Advanced Disposal Wants Clay County Residents to Donate Old Cell Phones in Honor of Veterans Day
Advanced Disposal Acquires MOR Recycling and Carting, Inc., Growing South Carolina Footprint
Advanced Disposal Bag Ladies Recycle 10,000 Bottles and Cans at 26.2 with Donna Marathon
Sustainable Energy Solutions LLC Begins Electrical Generation Project at Wolf Creek Landfill in Dry Branch, Georgia
Rotary Club of Orange Park and Advanced Disposal Team Up and Tee Off
Advanced Disposal Unveils Newly Remodeled Cobb County Transfer Station
Advanced Disposal Acquires Curly Waste Disposal, Expanding Footprint in Putnam County and Adding Transfer Station
Advanced Disposal to Make Georgiana Cleaner and Greener Starting April 1.
Advanced Disposal Acquires Countywide Waste Disposal, Expanding Footprint in Baker County
Advanced Disposal Refinances Credit Facility
Advanced Disposal To Make Dooly County Cleaner and Greener Starting Monday
Advanced Disposal Selected to Host Tour of Recycling Center in Williamson County
Advanced Disposal Opens Linden Transfer Station
Advanced Disposal Restructures, Promoting Two Key Executives
2010
Southeast Company Proud to Celebrate 10 Year Anniversary
“Bag Ladies” Help the Race to End Breast Cancer “Go Green” by Collecting 10,000 bottles
Advanced Disposal Acquires B&W Waste, Adding Transfer Station to Middle Georgia Operations
Advanced Disposal Selects Morris Logan as 2010 Corporate Employee of the Year
Turkey Trot Landfill Officially Opens in Washington County
Advanced Disposal Gives 19-Ton, Holiday Gift to Local College
Advanced Disposal Partners with Cell Phones for Soldiers in Honor of Veterans Day
Advanced Disposal Acquires Metro Hauling Services, Adds to Greater Atlanta Commercial Services Business
Advanced Disposal Produces Gopher Tortoise Relocation Movie
Advanced Disposal Awarded City of Pelham Solid Waste and Recycling Collection Contract
Advanced Disposal Acquires Third Polk County Company, Growing its Commercial Services Business
Advanced Disposal Grows its Commercial Services in Charlotte, with Acquisition of Construction Waste Services
Advanced Disposal Begins Mission to Make North Carolina Cleaner and Greener in Huntersville
Advanced Disposal Makes Second Acquisition in Polk County, Florida
Advanced Disposal Acquires Southland Sanitation and Expands into South Carolina Marketplace
Advanced Disposal's Bag Ladies to Sing the Song of Recycling at Sunday's Concert on the Green
Advanced Disposal Bag Ladies are 'Dancin' in the Streets'
Advanced Disposal Pitches in for the Tallahassee Chamber of Commerce Green & Clean Tallahassee Earth Day Event
Wolf Creek Landfill Helps Local Elementary Schools Celebrate 40th Anniversary of Earth Day
Advanced Disposal Pitches in for Dozens of Earth Day Events
Advanced Disposal Adds 21 Items to St. Johns County Recycling Collection List
Advanced Disposal Adds Fore Recycling to Grow Mississippi Operations
Advanced Disposal Pitches in At Crystal Springs Clean Up to Celebrate 40th Anniversary of Earth Day
Advanced Disposal's Jeff Pope Appointed as a Board Member for Keeping Pasco Beautiful
Advanced Disposal Strengthens Commitment to Recycling With Purchase of Sumrall Recycling
Advanced Disposal Adds Materials Recycling Facility to its Nashville Footprint
Advanced Disposal Acquires Trash Taxi and Expands North Florida Footprint
Advanced Disposal to Clean Up After Auburn's Next Victory
Advancded Disposal Completes Refinancing of Its Existing Credit Racility
The City of Smyrna Will Change Commercial Solid Waste Providers
Media Kit
Investor Relations
Suppliers
Suppliers
Investor Relations
News
Careers
About
Please confirm your ZIP code:
For Business
Collection Services
Garbage
Recycling
Special Waste
Construction & Demolition
Disposal & Recycling Services
Waste Disposal
Find a Facility
Check availability in your area:
For Home
Curbside Collection
Garbage
Recycling
Yard Waste
Bulk Pickup
Electronic Recycling
Household Hazardous Waste
Roll-Off Container Rental
Recycle Right
Kudos
Find a Facility
Check availability in your area:
For Government
Collection Services
Waste Removal
Recycling
Yard Waste
Bulk Waste
Disposal & Recycling Services
Waste Disposal
Recycling
Special Waste
Privatization
Recycle Right
Kudos
Find a Facility
Check availability in your area:
For Mother Earth
Customer Care
Customer Care Form
Request Services Form
Stay Informed
Service Standards
FAQs
Business Services
Find A Transfer Station
Attention Customers: We're excited to announce that Waste Management, North America's leading environmental solutions provider, has acquired Advanced Disposal. Learn what this means for you here.
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Your safety matters.
Advanced Disposal Services, Inc. and its subsidiaries ("Advanced Disposal," "we," "our," "us" or similar phrases) has tremendous respect for your non-public personal information, and protecting your personal information is one of our top priorities. We respect the privacy of our customers and other users who access this website to learn about or interact with us concerning the collection, storage, access and use of their personal and business information. This privacy statement explains our privacy practices, including how we use the personal information we receive from you. By accessing our website, you agree to the Advanced Disposal privacy policy. It is important that you review this privacy policy prior to registering on or using our website.
Advanced Disposal reserves the right to change, supplement, update or modify this privacy policy at any time without notice at the sole discretion of Advanced Disposal. In the event we modify or change our privacy policy, the modified policy will be posted on our website. The most current privacy policy will apply to all data and other information collected on the website, no matter what version of the privacy policy was in effect when the information was collected.
1. Personal Information Collected by Advanced Disposal We collect your personal information because it helps us deliver a superior level of customer service. It enables us to give you convenient access to our services and focus on categories of greatest interest to you. In addition, your personal information helps us keep you posted on our latest services, information and events that you might like to hear about.
We may collect personal information about you from the following sources: (i) information we receive from you pursuant to any service agreement or other agreement with Advanced Disposal, such as your name, address, telephone number or business information; (ii) information we receive from you through our website, such as your name, address, email address, telephone number, payment information and your activity while using or reviewing our websites; (iii) information about your transactions with us or information about the services performed by us, our affiliates, or others, such as information concerning your payment history or information about your site location for service, billing and credit card information; and (iv) information we receive from publicly recorded documents.
In addition, we may ask for your personal information when you’re discussing a service issue on the phone with an associate or when purchasing service. We may also collect certain personal information for market research purposes to gain a better understanding of our customers in order for us to provide more valuable service.
We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 for marketing purposes, but because some information is collected electronically, it can appear to be the personal information of the website user, and will be treated as such by this privacy policy. If a child under 13 submits personal information to Advanced Disposal and we learn that that personal information is the information of a child under 13, we will attempt to delete the information as soon as possible.
2. Use and Disclosure of Your Personal Information by Advanced Disposal Advanced Disposal will use personally identifiable information voluntarily submitted to us to respond to requests you make of us for service or to contact you in connection with the service being provided to you by Advanced Disposal. Additionally, we may use that information to determine how we can improve our website, business and services and to market our services. As a general rule, we will not sell or rent your personal or business information to any third party, except as described below or in connection with effectively maintaining and operating the website.
Advanced Disposal may disclose your personal information to others when we believe, in good faith, that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to comply with the law or to protect the safety of our customers, employees or property and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order or legal process. We may respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process by disclosing your personal information and other related information, if necessary. We also may choose to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. In addition, we may collect and possibly share personal information and any other additional information available to us in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of the Advanced Disposal terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.
Advanced Disposal will share your personal information with our corporate affiliates to carry out transactions you request or to make our business more responsive to your needs, and we may disclose your personal information to non-affiliated third parties that perform services on our behalf. Advanced Disposal may also disclose your personal information to third parties where it is necessary for completing the transactions that you authorize and in order to verify the existence and condition of your account for a third party. We reserve the right to provide non-personal identifying information to third parties. Except as described above, we will not disclose your personal information to other third parties unless you have provided consent.
3. Payment System If you are using our website to access our electronic payment system, we may request certain financial information so that we may effect the payment transaction. Our payment system may collect, store and use personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, credit card number, bank routing and account number, Advanced Disposal account number and email address to process your payments. In addition, the payment system will also collect information regarding the actual bill payment transactions, including the dates and amounts paid. Advanced Disposal will store and protect this information in the same manner that we store and protect other personal customer information.
Advanced Disposal will typically send emails regarding your bill availability, or we may attach your bill to an email, depending on the choice you have made. We may also send confirmation emails regarding payments and certain types of maintenance. Confirmation emails help guard against fraudulent use of the system.
Advanced Disposal will record your use of the payment system to the extent that we are aware of when login occurs. We will also keep statistics about how the payment system is used. This information helps us plan better services and improve system performance.
4. Security Advanced Disposal is concerned with the security of the data and information we collect, and we use commercially reasonable physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to help ensure the security, integrity and privacy of all personal information. We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide service to you or in order to do their jobs.
We use encrypted transmission (Secure Socket Layer - SSL) for all transactions on our website. If we attach your bill to an email, we use encrypted Adobe Acrobat PDF files. However, due to the inherent insecurity of the Internet, no security measures should be viewed as 100 percent effective in all circumstances. Advanced Disposal cannot absolutely guarantee against a breach of its security or the actions of third parties who may seek to obtain unauthorized access to personal information. All transmissions of your personal information are done at your own risk.
You can help us by also taking precautions to protect your personal account, passwords and other personal information when using our website or the Internet in general. Change your passwords often, using a combination of letters and numbers.
5. Links to Other Websites Our website may contain links to websites that are provided and maintained by third parties and that are not subject to this privacy policy. Please review the privacy policies on those websites. We make no representations concerning, and are not responsible for, any such third-party websites or their privacy policies or practices.
6. Cookies As is standard practice on many corporate websites, our website uses "cookies" and other technologies to help us understand which parts of our websites are the most popular, where our visitors are going, and how much time they spend there. The use of cookies or similar technologies helps us to improve our service to you. Our cookies do not collect your personal information. Your browser can most likely be configured to notify you when cookies will be received and offer you the option of refusing cookies. If you reject cookies, you may still use our website, but your ability to use some areas may be limited. Advanced Disposal will not share cookies with any third party other than as set forth in this privacy policy, and we will not place shared cookies or customer profiling banner advertisements on our website.
If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact our IT Department or Legal Department at (904) 737-7900.
Advanced Disposal, now part of Waste Management
Waste Management, based in Houston, Texas, is the leading provider of comprehensive waste management environmental services in North America. Through its subsidiaries, Waste Management provides collection, transfer, disposal services, and recycling and resource recovery.  It is also a leading developer, operator and owner of landfill gas-to-energy facilities in the United States.  Waste Management’s customers include residential, commercial, industrial, and municipal customers throughout North America.  To learn more information about Waste Management, visit www.wm.com.
About Us
About
Careers
News
My Account
Pay My Bill
Customer Care
Find a Facility
FAQs
Products & Services
For Business
For Home
For Government
For Mother Earth
© 2020 Advanced Disposal Services, Inc.
All Rights Reserved.
Privacy
|
Terms of Use
|
Sitemap
|
Accessibility
You have a choice to make. No pressure.
I'm interested in:
Commercial Services
Residential Services
Okay maybe a little pressure.
I'm a:
Municipal Resident - My local government selects my solid waste provider for me
Subscription Customer - I choose my service provider
It's not you, it's your zip code. We're sorry but we do not currently provide service for your location.
CLICK HERE to find the nearest Advanced Disposal facility.
Stay Informed...
Get notified of service alerts, new services, community news and special offers for your area.
Subscribe today!
If you are a residential customer, please don’t forget to regularly visit both your local municipality’s solid waste page as well as our local facility and your community’s individual page (scroll down slightly on your local facility page to the Guidelines for Municipal Customers tab) and click on the link for your community’s garbage collection guidelines and holiday schedule.
Thank you!
I am providing Advanced Disposal with the above email and/or telephone number and hereby expressly agree that I am authorizing the communication by phone, email, and/or text of service alerts, promotions and other Advanced Disposal communications to be sent to the above address and/or phone number. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization. Upon receiving a text message, you have the option to Reply STOP to cancel, HELP for help. Standard message and data rates apply.
We have added you to our alert list.
LEGAL NOTICE: You are leaving Advanced Disposal's website. Links are provided as a public service and are for informational purposes only. No endorsement is made or implied. Clicking on "Continue" will take you to a website that is outside the control of Advanced Disposal. You are solely responsible for your interactions with such websites.
To find and apply to available Advanced Disposal positions, click "Continue".
LEGAL NOTICE: You are leaving Advanced Disposal's website however clicking on "Continue" will take you to our official recruit management website by ADP, LLC.
Links are provided as a public service and are for informational purposes only. No endorsement is made or implied. You are solely responsible for your interactions with such websites.
